<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources xmlns:xliff="http://schemas.android.com/tools">
    <!--title and content of PP-->
    <string name="privacy_policy">Privacy policy</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_content_one"><b>Introduction</b>\n\nWe, “TCT Mobile International Limited ” (hereinafter to the referred to as “we”, “our”, or “TCT”) respect your concerns about privacy. This Privacy Policy explains our policies and procedures regarding personal and other information about our customers.We intend to provide you with a level of comfort and confidence in how we collect, use, disclose, and safeguard personal and other information that we collect or that you provide to us. This Privacy Policy also explains how you can contact us if you have any questions or concerns about your personal information.\n\n<b>Scope</b>\n\nThis Privacy Policy describes in detail our policy and practices regarding collection, use and disclosure of information that we collect through our websites, software applications, social media pages, e-mail messages, and your purchase or use of our products or service, or personal information that you otherwise provide to  us.\nBy providing personal information to us, accessing our website or by using our products or services, you acknowledge that you have read and understood this Privacy Policy and agreed to the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy.\nYour personal information will be stored and processed on secure servers in the European Economic Area (“EEA”). Due to the global nature of the internet, your personal information may be transferred to countries outside the EEA whose legal systems do not offer the same level of protection for your data as the laws of European Union and more specifically France, and by using our websites, software applications, social media pages, e-mail messages, and your purchase or use of our products or service, you agree to such terms.\nWe will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your personal information is stored and processed securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy and applicable laws.\n\n<b>The personal information we collect</b>\n\nThis Privacy Policy applies to personal information, which is information that can be used to contact or identify a single person.\nWe collect information that you give us. We receive and store safely any information when you create an account ID, purchase our products or services, download a software update, contact us or participate in an online survey. \nWe collect automatic information. We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us.\nWe collect information used in e-mail communications. To help us make e-mails more useful and interesting, we often receive a confirmation when you open e-mail from our e-shopping website if your computer supports such capabilities. We also compare our customer list to lists received from other companies, in an effort to avoid sending unnecessary messages to our customers. \nWe collect information from other sources. We might receive information about you from other sources, which are duly authorized by yourself to transfer such information to third parties and add it to our account information.\n\n<b>How we use your personal information</b>\n\n<li>The personal information we collect allows us to keep you posted on our latest product announcements, software updates, and upcoming events. If you don’t want to be on our mailing list, you can opt out anytime by updating your preferences.</li>\n<li>We also use personal information to help us create, develop, operate, deliver, and improve our products, services, content, advertising and continually improve your user experience</li>\n<li>We may use your personal information to repond to your inquiries and fulfill your requests.</li>\n<li>We may use your personal information, including date of birth, to verify identity, assist with identification of users, and to determine appropriate services. For example, we may use date of birth to determine the age of user account holders.</li>\n<li>From time to time, we may use your personal information to send important notices, such as communications about purchases and changes to our terms, conditions, and policies. Because this information is important to your interaction with us, you may not opt out of receiving these communications.</li>\n<li>We may also use personal information for internal purposes such as auditing, data analysis, and research to improve our products, services, and customer communications.</li>\n\n<b>Collection and Use of Non-Personal Information</b>\n\nWe may also collect information, which does not, on its own, allow direct association with any specific individual. We may collect, use, transfer and disclose non-personal information for any purpose. Here are some examples of non-personal data that we may collect:\n<li>Non-personal data such as occupation, language, zip code, area code, unique device identifier, referrer URL, location, and the time zone where one of our products is used so that we can better understand customer behavior and improve our products, services, and advertising.</li>\n<li>Non-personal data regarding customer activities on our website, cloud services and the app store and from our other products and services. This information is aggregated and used to help us to provide more useful information to our customers and to understand which parts of our website, products, and services are of most interest. For the purposes of this privacy policy, this type of data is considered to be non-personal information.</li>\n<li>Details of how you use our services, including search queries, which may be used to improve the relevancy of results provided by our services. Except in limited instances to ensure quality of our services over the Internet, such information will not be associated with your IP address.</li>\n<li>With your explicit consent, we may collect data about how you use your device and applications in order to help app developers to improve their apps.</li>\nIf we do combine non-personal information with personal information, the combined information will be treated as personal information for as long as it remains combined.\n\n</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_content_two"><b>Cookies and Other Technologies</b>\n\nOur websites, online services, interactive applications, email messages, and advertisements may use “cookies” and other technologies. These technologies help us better understand user behavior, tell us which parts of our websites people have visited, and facilitate and measure the effectiveness of advertisements and web searches. We treat information collected by cookies and other technologies as non personal information. However, to the extent that IP addresses or similar identifiers are considered personal information by local law, we also treat these identifiers as personal information. Similarly, to the extent that non-personal information is combined with personal information, we treat the combined information as personal information for the purposes of this Privacy Policy.\nTCT and our partners also use cookies and other technologies to remember personal information when you use our website, online services, and applications. Our goal in these cases is to make your experience with TCT more convenient and personal. For example, knowing someone using your computer or device has shopped for a certain product or used a particular service helps us make our advertising and email communications more relevant to your interests.\nYou may configure your browser to accept all cookies, reject all cookies, or notify you when a cookie is sent. Each browser is different, so check the "Help" menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences. For example, on Microsoft Internet Explorer you can disable or delete cookies by selecting “Tools/Internet Options”.\nIn some of our email messages, we use a “click-through URL” linked to content on our website. When customers click one of these URLs, they pass through a separate web server before arriving at the destination page on our website. We track this click-through data to help us determine interest in particular topics and measure the effectiveness of our customer communications. If you prefer not to be tracked in this way, you should not click text or graphic links in the email messages.\n\n<b>Do We Share the Information?</b>\n\nWe do not share personal information with companies, organizations and individuals outside of TCT unless one of the following circumstances applies. \nTCT may share personal information with your consent.\nWe may disclose personal information to our affiliates when necessary to perform services on our or on your behalf.\nWe cooperate with companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include fulfilling orders, delivering packages, sending postal mail and e-mail, removing repetitive information from customer lists, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, providing search results and links (including paid listings and links), processing credit card payments, and providing customer service. They have access to personal information needed to perform their functions, but may not use it for other purposes.\nWe will share personal information with organizations or individuals outside our organization if we believe that access, use, preservation or disclosure of the information is reasonably necessary to: \n<li>meet any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request.</li>\n<li>detect, prevent or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues.</li>\n<li>protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of our users or the public, as required or permitted by law.</li>\nYour personal information may be transferred to, and stored at, a destination outside the EEA within the TCT group. It may also be processed by staff operating outside the EEA who work for us or for one of our suppliers. We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your personal information is treated securely and in accordance with this privacy policy.\n\n<b>Security and Transparency</b>\n\nWe will endeavor to take all reasonable physical, technical and organizational measures and procedures to safeguard and secure the personal information we collect through our products and our website.\nWe work hard to protect our company, reputation and our users from unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of personal information that we hold. In particular:\n<li>We review our information collection, storage and processing practices, including physical security measures, to guard against unauthorized access to systems;</li>\n<li>We use encryption where appropriate;</li>\n<li>We use password protection where appropriate;</li>\n<li>We restrict access to personal information to our employees, contractors and agents who need to know that information in order to process it for us and who are subject to strict contractual confidentiality obligations. They may be disciplined or their contract may be terminated if they fail to meet these obligations.</li>\nHowever,</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_content_three">these measures do not release you from taking appropriate steps to keep your personal information safe and secure, in particular by avoiding obvious user ID\'s or passwords, by ensuring that you do not disclose your password(s) or grant any other person access to your user account and your personal information, and any other protective measures applicable.\nRegarding transparency, our goal is to be clear what information we collect, so that you can make choices about how it is used.\nIf you share your personal information through one of our websites or devices with a third party account, such as Facebook, Google + or Twitter, please note that the privacy of your personal information will be managed respectively by one of those third parties. We are not responsible for any damages due to any data loss, damage or in-fringement that may occur on your third party profiles over which we have no control.\nAny personal information or content that you voluntarily disclose while using our website or devices and which can be viewed by members of third party applications or sites (such as chat areas, in messages), becomes publicly viewable and can be collected ,viewed and used by others. You are responsible for the personal information you choose to share or submit in these instance.\n\n<b>Children</b>\n\nWe understand the importance of taking extra precautions to protect the privacy and safety of children using our products and services. Accordingly, we do not knowingly collect, use or disclose personal information from children under 13, or equivalent minimum age in the relevant jurisdiction, without verifiable parental consent. If we learn that, we have collected the personal information of a child under 13, or equivalent minimum age depending on jurisdiction, without first receiving verifiable parental consent we will take steps to delete the information as soon as possible.\n\n<b>Changes</b>\n\n</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_content_four">Our Privacy Policy may change from time to time.  We will post any Privacy Policy changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice (including, for certain services, email notification of Privacy Policy changes). We will also keep prior versions of this Privacy Policy in an archive for your review.\nThe current version is dated <xliff:g example="25/03/2016" id="date">%1$s</xliff:g>.\n\n</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_content_five"><b>Retention of Personal Information</b>\n\nWe keep your personal information for a limited duration necessary to fulfill the purposes outlined in this Privacy Policy unless a longer retention period is required or permitted by law and only for the purposes defined above. Once the purpose is achieved, all personal information is deleted in a safe and secure mode.\n\n<b>Location-Based Services</b>\n\nTo provide location-based services on TCT products, TCT and our partners and licensees may collect, use, and share precise location data, including the real-time geographic location of your device. Where available, location-based services may use GPS, Bluetooth, and your IP Address, along with crowd-sourced Wi-Fi hotspot and cell tower locations, and other technologies to determine your devices’ approximate location. Unless you provide consent, this location data is collected anonymously in a form that does not personally identify you and is used by TCT and our partners and licensees to provide and improve location-based products and services. For example, your device may share its geographic location with application providers when you opt in to their location services.\n\n<b>Third Party Sites and Services</b>\n\nTCT websites, products, applications, and services may contain links to third-party websites, products, and services. Our products and services may also use or offer products or services from third parties. Information collected by third parties, which may include such things as location data or contact details, is governed by their privacy practices. We encourage you to learn about the privacy practices of those third parties.\n\n<b>Your rights: Access, Edit, Block</b>\n\nYou can access, review and edit your personal information at any time by logging into your user account, visiting your user profile or by contacting us directly. Should you require us to edit or delete your personal information, we may ask you to provide us with evidence of your identity before we can act on your request.\nYou can also have your data deleted or blocked, as appropriate, should you believe that your data is inaccurate.\nFor all and any requests as defined above, you may send your request to the following email address: privacy@alcatelonetouch.com\nUnder certain jurisdictions and data protection laws, you may have the right to request details of your personal information, which we hold, about you or to request the correction or deletion of your personal information.\nPlease help us to ensure that we hold about you is accurate and up to date. If you think that any we have stored about you is incorrect or incomplete, please contact us at privacy@alcatelonetouch.com or write to our customer services department.\n\n<b>Privacy Questions</b>\n\nIf you have any questions or concerns about our Privacy Policy or data processing or if you would like to make a complaint about a possible breach of local privacy laws, please contact us. You can always contact us by phone at the relevant phone number or email for your country.\nAll communications are examined and replies are issued where appropriate as soon as possible. If you are unsatisfied with the reply received, you may refer your complaint to the relevant regulator in your jurisdiction. If you ask us, we will endeavor to provide you with information about relevant complaint avenues, which may be applicable to your circumstances.</string>
    <!--title and content of TC-->
    <string name="terms_and_conditions_of_use">TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF USE</string>
    <string name="terms_and_conditions_of_use_content_one">These Terms and Conditions of use tell you how you may use the User Center application and online service (“Service”) to access.\nThis Service is published by TCT Mobile International Limited hereinafter referred to as “ALCATEL ONETOUCH”, registered at Room 19 12 A, Tower 3, China Hong Kong City, 33 Canton Road, Tsim Sha Tsui, Kowloon, Hong-Kong.\nPlease read through these Terms and Conditions of Use and our Privacy Policy  (hereinafter “Terms and Conditions”) carefully. These Terms and Conditions are a contract between you and TCT Mobile International Limited and may be amended from time to time. If you don’t agree to the Terms and Conditions, do not use the Service. If you do use the Service, you accept and agree to these Terms and Conditions.\nThe purpose and some content of this Service may not be adapted for minors. By accessing this Website, you guarantee that you are not a minor and are entitled by the law of your country of domicile to access the Website.\n\n<b>Guidelines of Use</b>\n\nWhen you create an ONETOUCH account or register e-warranty, we will ask you to provide us with some personal information, such as your email address, nickname, location and your profile photo. Your personal information will be collected, stored and processed in accordance with our Privacy Policy and in compliance with the governing law, which you shall read before using this Service.\nYour email address will be your ONETOUCH user name, which you will use to log-into your account. We do not display your email address to other users of the Service.\nYou may also log in with a 3rd party account. In case you login with a 3rd party account such as Facebook, Twitter or Google+, we will use the registered email in those third party as your user name. Please note that if you register with your third party account, respectively their terms and conditions and their privacy policy will apply respectively.\nBy registering you will also benefit from the a range of Services that we will offer you, and notably after sales services, hotline, e warranty and you can get in touch with us any time you wish.\nFor the after sales services, you will find all necessary addresses worldwide of our repair centers.\nFor hot line, there is list of phone numbers that you can dial for an efficient and immediate support and consumer experience.\nIf you want to store your data of your smartphone, such as contacts, photos, call logs, SMS within the 2G free storage space, and access it with other devices, such as your PC or tablets, you should create an ONETOUCH account.\nBy registering into the Service, you will have direct access to your phone information, IMEI, the model and the activation date, which will automatically benefit you.\nOur goal is to help you store and access your own data freely.\n\n<b>Intellectual Property</b>\n\nExcept for the user generated content if any, the Service, including all copyrights, trademarks, and other intellectual property rights therein are protected by intellectual property rights and are owned by ALCATEL ONETOUCH or a third party.\nYou may not reproduce, distribute, modify or create derivative works of, publicly display (including by framing any content), or commercially exploit any part of the Service except as necessary to view the content therein and to create a reasonable number of copies of portions of such content (without modification) for your personal, non-commercial use.\nIf you believe that any content of the application violates any third party intellectual property rights, please contact us immediately. We, as soon as we receive your notification, will take necessary action to cease any such violation and remove any illicit content.\nALCATEL ONETOUCH trademark, the logo and any other trademarks, service marks, graphics, and logos used in connection with this Website are trademarks or registered trademarks of ALCATEL ONETOUCH or its licensors. Other trademarks, service marks, graphics, and logos used in connection with the Website may be the trademarks of their respective owners. You are granted no right or license with respect to any of the aforesaid trademarks and any use of such trademarks.\nIn the event of any violations of the above, ALCATEL ONETOUCH reserves the right to ask you to immediately stop or rectify the unlawful use, or, should the unlawful use and/or violation continue, ALCATEL ONETOUCH reserves the right to file a claim against you.\n\n</string>
    <string name="terms_and_conditions_of_use_content_two"><b>Data Protection and Privacy</b>\n\nAny information which you provide to us from which ALCATEL ONETOUCH can identify you are held and processed in accordance with our Privacy Policy.\nIn connection with your use of the Service, you may share with us your email address for further communication between you and ALCATEL ONETOUCH. Prior to giving out your email address, please review our Privacy Policy in order to understand how we collect and use information about you when you access, visit or use the Website.\nYour personal information will be collected, stored and processed in accordance with our Privacy Policy and the applicable law. \n\n<b>Warranty disclaimer; limitation of liabilities</b>\n\nThe Service is provided by ALCATEL ONETOUCH "as is."\nTo the full extent permissible by applicable law, neither ALCATEL ONETOUCH nor its partners, suppliers, or affiliates make any representations or warranties of any kind, express or implied, as to the operation of the Service, its contents, or any information made available by or through the Service. In addition, ALCATEL ONETOUCH and its partners disclaim all warranties with respect to the Service, express or implied, including but not limited to the implied warranties of merchantability, title, fitness for a particular purpose and non-infringement. Furthermore, ALCATEL ONETOUCH does not warrant that use of the Service will be uninterrupted, available at any time or from any particular location, secure or error-free, that defects will be corrected, or that the Service is free of viruses or other potentially harmful components. You shall be responsible for backing up your own system.\nALCATEL ONETOUCH does not make any other promises or warranties about the Service and in particular does not warrant and shall not be liable for any claim that results from a decision made by ALCATEL ONETOUCH to remove or refuse to process any information or content, to warn you, to suspend or terminate your access to the Service, or to take any other action during the investigation of a suspected violation or as a result of ALCATEL ONETOUCH conclusion that a violation of these Terms and Conditions has occurred; or it relates to loss of income, business or profits, or any loss of data or corruption of data in connection with your use of the Application or the Service.\nIn no event will ALCATEL ONETOUCH accept liability for any description, including liability for negligence (except for personal injury or death), for any damages or losses whatsoever (including, without limitation, loss of business, revenue, profits, or consequential loss) resulting from the use of or your inability to use the Service.\nIf you breach these Terms and Conditions, you will be liable to ALCATEL ONETOUCH, its directors, officers, employees, affiliates, agents, contractors, and licensors for any claim arising out of your breach. You will also be liable for any action taken by ALCATEL ONETOUCH as part of its investigation of a suspected violation of these Terms and Conditions, or as a result of its findings or decision that a violation of these Terms and Conditions has occurred.\n\n</string>
    <string name="terms_and_conditions_of_use_content_three"><b>Links to third-party sites</b>\n\nThe Service may also contain links to websites, which are not under the control of or maintained by ALCATEL ONETOUCH. ALCATEL ONETOUCH is not responsible for the content of those websites. ALCATEL ONETOUCH provides these links for your convenience only and does not necessarily endorse the material on these sites.\nThe use by you of these third party websites creates a direct relationship between you and such third parties. It is therefore your responsibility to read and comply with such third parties privacy policies and their terms and conditions, which apply to their websites. All and any claims with regards to such third party websites or content found on websites shall be directed to such third parties. \n\n<b>Changes</b>\n\nALCATEL ONETOUCH reserves the right to modify these Terms and Conditions at any time. Such modifications and additional terms and conditions will be communicated to you and, if accepted, they will be effective immediately and will be incorporated into these Terms and Conditions. In the event that you refuse to accept such changes, you shall cease to access the Service and the Application immediately. Should you continue to use the Service despite your disagreement to the Terms and Conditions or to any changes thereof, ALCATEL ONETOUCH shall not be liable for any claims resulting thereof.\n\n<b>Governing law. Jurisdiction</b>\n\nThis Service is controlled and operated by ALCATEL ONETOUCH offices based in PR China. By accessing this Service, you agree that the laws of PR China will apply to the matters relating to the use of this Service, without regard to principles of the conflicts of laws.\nIn the event of a dispute, disagreement between ALCATEL ONETOUCH and you arising out of or in connection with your use of the Service, the parties shall attempt, promptly and in good faith, to resolve any such dispute. If we are unable to resolve any such dispute within a reasonable time (not to exceed thirty (30) days), then either party may submit such controversy or dispute to the competent courts of PR China.\n\n<b>Miscellaneous</b>\n\nIf any of the provisions of these Terms and Conditions are held by a court or other tribunal of competent jurisdiction to be void or unenforceable, such provisions shall be limited or eliminated to the minimum extent necessary and replaced with a valid provision that best embodies the intent of these Terms and Conditions, so that these shall remain in full force and effect.\nThese Terms and Conditions constitute the entire agreement between you and ALCATEL ONETOUCH with regard to your use of the Service, and any and all other written or oral agreements or understandings previously existing between you and ALCATEL ONETOUCH with respect to such use are hereby superseded and cancelled.</string>

    <string name="share_location">Share location</string>
    <string name="informed_content">Experience improvement makes your phone better by sharing diagnostics and usage data to Alcatel. This won\'t be used to identify you and allows our hardworking teams to improve things like apps, performance, errors and features for future updates. \n\n For more info see our  </string>
    <string name="terms_and_condition">Terms and conditions</string>
    <string name="and">&#160;and&#160;</string>
    <string name="more_info">For more information,please read our &#160;</string>
</resources>